<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shibin Li on Universal</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/authors/shibin-li/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Shibin Li on Universal</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 21:49:20 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/authors/shibin-li/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Congratulations in Science 2022</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/science2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/science2022/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;During the aging process, the brain experiences a significant loss of hypocretin (Hcrt)/orexin neurons. The high excitability of aged hypocretin neurons, characterized by depolarization of the resting potential, along with the adaptive upregulation of prepro-Hcrt mRNA expression, leads to fragmented sleep during aging. The aged Hcrt neurons with high excitability express a reduced M-current mediated by KCNQ2/3 channels, and the decreased expression of KCNQ2 impairs the neuron’s repolarization capacity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congratulations in Science Advance 2020</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/science_asvance2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/science_asvance2020/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(A) Distribution of cell subpopulations based on the aggregated data from all samples. (B) tSNE plots of intracellular protein expression, including IκB (left), pSTAT6 (middle), and pCREB (right), in the control group and the optogenetic stimulation group. (C) Comparison of the distribution of innate immune cells in the circulatory system, including NK1.1+ NK cells, MHCII+ dendritic cells, Ly6CLow patrolling monocytes, and Ly6CHi inflammatory/phagocytic monocytes, at baseline (black bar graphs) and during CRH neuron activation (red bar graphs). (D) Comparison of the distribution of adaptive immune cells in the circulatory system at baseline (black bar graphs) and during CRH neuron activation (red bar graphs), including a decrease in B lymphocytes (B220+). TH1 TBet+ cells and CD4+ T cells also decreased.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
